<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Ronak Rathore</title>
    <link>https://ronakr14.github.io/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Ronak Rathore</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 18:36:10 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ronakr14.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Python Metaclasses</title>
      <link>https://ronakr14.github.io/blogs/python_metaclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 18:36:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ronakr14.github.io/blogs/python_metaclass/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction-to-python-metaclasses&#34;&gt;Introduction to Python Metaclasses&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Metaclasses are an advanced and somewhat lesser-known feature in Python, but they hold immense power. In essence, metaclasses are the classes of classes. They define how classes behave, just as classes define how instances behave. While regular classes in Python are blueprints for creating objects, metaclasses are blueprints for creating classes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-use-metaclasses&#34;&gt;Why Use Metaclasses?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You might ask: Why do we need a class for a class? Metaclasses allow for customization of class creation. By using them, you can:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Intrusion Detection System V0.1</title>
      <link>https://ronakr14.github.io/projects/nids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 18:10:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ronakr14.github.io/projects/nids/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A binary classification machine learning model for Intrusion Detection System.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A special thanks to Satish Kamble.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This machine learning model for binary classification identifies users on our network system and divides them into benign and malignant categories. Every network, whether it is private or public, is vulnerable to assaults that stop the regular flow of traffic on networks, as we all know. The fundamental goal of developing this architecture was to protect both public and private networks while warning the administrator of potential future harm.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
